Seongya
I...
My spiritual eyes were opened
In order of facial features
What happens if a ghost takes it away?
This
When you hear a sound, you have faith.
I start believing in ghosts
neck
I get lonely when I see you
If you see a ghost then
Everyone thinks you're a liar
Because no one believes me
That's why I feel lonely
Yeah
Because it's so lonely
There are people who want to be friends with ghosts.
You can't do that.
Ghosts and humans
The reason I want to be friends
It's usually just one
Because I want that body
What's on my face?
Ah... no
I saw it because it was pretty, because it was pretty
Coach
Do you know that you are a really strange person?
Why? no
Who can make an amateur like me
Are you bringing me out to a big game like this?
Aren’t you scared, Coach?
I'm quite scared right now.
Tseu-eup, is this place really serious?
Who wants you to win a medal?
Do what you always do, what you did at school
I'm not doing anything?
Just playing, at the archery range?
So do that
Playing with a bow next to Gyeonwoo
You don’t know, right?
Gyeonwoo, that guy
Sometimes I laugh while shooting an archery, because of you
Kids who smile last a long time
I want to see him for a long time
Write it
Because of Gyeonwoo’s grades
Are you using me now?
I love you
- Buy me some beef.
- If Gyeonwoo wins the gold medal,
- call
What are you doing, man?
I couldn't believe it
Bae Gyeon-woo, who defeated archery
Can you see everything here?
Yeah, that's how it happened.
Oh, does Heena know?
Are you playing archery again?
Yeah, I know
He says he forgives you?
It's Heena
I'm going out to Hallagi
I'm going to stop running away now
Hey Gyeonwoo
I'm still the same
I wish you were dead
Don't hurt too much
You said to Heena
It can't be like this
Heena, it all happened because of someone!
Hey, other people see it.
Stop it
Hey, no matter what
Say it with words
me too
I thought it was because of me?
So
I completely disappeared from his life.
He still wasn't happy at all
I'm trying to make someone unhappy
I'm not shooting a bow
I just do it because I like it.
Let's not be too complicated like this
Can’t everyone just do what they like?
We all like archery
What is the use of reciting harmony in these times?
It's chlorine!
Open the door!
Aunt!
Please give me the key to the prayer room!
What kind of modification is this again?
high school boys
The 70m record race begins.
Hey Gyeonwoo
If you're ready, let's go now.
Fighting Bae Gyeon-woo!
Gyeonwoo, cheer up, you can do it
Are you holding on tight like this?
Then
I don't think I'll lose
Because you are so warm
Now I am you
I will protect you
Oh, 2 points?
That's right
Wow, cool
Ah, the back of our Gyeonwoo’s head is handsome too.
Oh, pretty
Huh?
This is...
Bongsu can easily kill Gyeonwoo.
Are you giving me bad energy?
But what should I do?
Today, with our suppression method,
Because it is a day to protect each other.
To herd a cowherd
You have to win over me first.
Look at this?
If you don't shoot now, you'll be disqualified, Gyeonwoo.
Cowherd, you have to shoot
I mean archery
How do you feel when you do it?
ok
No matter how strong the wind blows
You can win it all with one arrow
Ah, wow...
1st place in high school male individual competition
Bae Gyeonwoo
Great!
Congratulations, Gyeonwoo!
Well done
Great!
one, two, three
I'll smile a little louder
two, three
That's enough, that's enough
Daily archery club member
Stick, stick, take a picture, I'll take a picture
- Huh? Ah...
- Seongah, go quickly.
- thank you
- Yes
Stick more, stick more
Okay, do your thing.
- I'll take a picture myself.
- Huh?
oh
Now, one, two, three
Smile, wait, wait, me too, me too!
huh?
Gikkippappa, man
Do it in moderation
one
one, two, three
The picture isn't that good, compared to before.
Let's go eat beef!
Hey, daily archery club member.
Let's go too
Oh, I have work to do at home.
Me, teacher, me too, first today...
Oh, oh, why!
Yeah, why? Let's go together!
Oh, it's not that other thing.
This, this
I want to show you grandma.
I think you'll like it
sorry
I'm sorry
Oh my
I'm sorry for that then
I'm more sorry
I'm sorry
Have a nice day, grandma.
Will you come with me?
No, hon, I'll go alone.
yes
Hey
Why are you so nice?
Buy me a lot of beef?
Even if you buy me less
I plan to eat a lot
Let's go!
let's go!
You don’t have to follow me today
I'll go alone
Yeah, I'm not following you.
- It's okay to be apart today.
- Yes
Uh, but...
Gyeonwoo, are you feeling uncomfortable?
Isn't there somewhere like that?
Uh, nothing at all?
Ah, thank goodness
What about you?
uh?
I feel like I'm flying
That's good
To ask the other person for harmony
I tried harmonization
Are you being killed again?
I drank alcohol, but it came back to my flesh.
What does this mean?
Being in harmony with you
It means it's a good thing.
Even while throwing flesh there
I didn't want to come together
How do I do this?
Maybe it's because we have the same roots
I heard there could be harmony.
walk like that
Where will the temple be destroyed?
Step harder...
Why does it look like that?
It's no big deal
It's no big deal, I was cursed
What kind of bastard are you?
Why do you harm the child!
Was it Seong-ah who hit with the harmony jutsu?
why?
Are you angry because I touched your new daughter?
You're not even a child?
If you're going to hate me, just hate me.
Does that work?
If you hate someone
The ring the person was wearing
The hat I often wore and the dog I raised
The neighborhood I live in
Even neighbors who say hello in the neighborhood
Gather it all together
I want to throw everything in the trash can, but only people
How can you hate me?
I can't
i hate everything
keep doing that
Are you going to live in hell?
yes
grandmother
I won a gold medal
My vision is just...
It was a bit bad
Still, I stayed focused.
Are you here?
yes
It's a pain in the ass
Hey there
My head hurts so much because of that.
Do you know?
Mistress
Even my eyes seem to hurt now
Like that
So why do you keep getting involved with me?
Avoid it
What if you avoid it?
Are you avoiding that one or that one?
Even though I can't win
baby
Are you tired of playing with your baby now?
Are you raising your voice because you did something good?
Boy
You were abandoned by your family, right?
After being used to make money, at a young age
- Chloride
- Oh, really.
The body giver is a fairy god.
Things like giving your body
Isn't that too harsh?
What on earth are you talking about?
Hey, you come out
Let's go out
Are you unfamiliar with me?
I'm not familiar with you
'Cause you're totally me
It was you who kicked me out and brought me in.
Alone like me
unhappy like me
You are cursed like me
Shut up!
Seongah, it’s different from you.
I was raised differently
and
From now on, I will raise you again.
With a heart held in my stomach for ten months
I'll put in my sincerity
I will never let you go now
There was black stain on Seongah’s clothes?
yes
My energy has become cloudy
I guess I'll get a refund
I'm talking about that fight.
Is there any way for me to get that instead?
None
If a person other than a shaman receives it, he or she will die.
Then tell me about that suppression method.
Can you please break it?
Please close my eyesight
Didn't you call me?
Yes, but...
Baby's safety comes first
That's more urgent
yes
let's see
Is it a human talisman?
There must be something that Seongah gave you?
ah!
Here it is
Is it real?
My mother took the place of the shaman Yeonhwa
That you raised me
Enough to raise it on behalf of someone else
Raising a child
It's not that easy.
It was strange, from the first time we met.
Doing the flower lantern dance
Just like we tried to sum it up before
It fit well
Yes
This is a dance I learned under the same mother-in-law.
It's bound to be right
If you put it that way
I could become that bad too
Isn't it there?
You might not believe it, but
He was a very kind and gentle person.
So I get used a lot
I got hurt a lot
There's a reason the general's sore fingers
But
no need to worry
Because there is someone who can make it right.
Even if the stream takes a wrong turn
As long as the sea holds up, there's no problem.
yes
- I can't wake up, let's give up.
- Yes?
You two are very strong human talismans.
The desire to protect each other is so strong
There is no room for other spells
No, what should I do then?
Um...
Let's do it like this
Put this item in the Chilseong Temple
I'll give you my respect
The Chilseongshin is the god who governs our lifespan.
You are the Lord of my body
It's a human talisman, not just for you.
He will protect Seong-ah at the same time.
Okay then, please.
From now on
You should never get involved with ghosts.
First, you must not get involved with evil spirits.
Second, even if they are involved
Even if I die, I can't see blood
When skin irritation occurs
I can't control the situation
Am I going to die?
I'll be happy if I die
Being unable to live or die
That's the problem
For the time being, I think your body is glass.
Live carefully
With the blessings of Chilseong
Until the morgue and morgue are all safely closed.
You can do it, right?
Let's try it
Hey there
That place keeps looking strange to me.
What did you do again?
Because my energy was mixed during the harmony technique.
Why?
Do I look like the devil?
A wooden box about this size.
The lid is tied to a white cloth so that it cannot be opened.
I'm carrying a box
It's a shame
I have to look like the devil
Huh?
He's a good brother
hello
Shall I show you my baby?
- baby
- Baby?
That's cute, baby
So cute, right?
Ah, surprise, surprise
Ah, buy...
Ah, you were a person.
What are you saying to me?
No, no, no
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Huh? you, you
It's crazy, really!
Looks like a good bucket of money
Yes?
What do you wear?
uh?
nerd
‘You bastard, give me some pocket money’
‘Reply’
'Answer, answer'
'Do it quickly, won't you reply quickly?'
‘Answer, reply, quickly, answer’
‘Wait until you get there’
From now on
You should never get involved with ghosts.
For the time being, I think your body is glass.
Live carefully
Hey, Young and Handsome
Are you coming now?
- Yes
- Ah...
Handsome, listen carefully.
Fairy of Heaven and Earth is going to be very sick sooner or later.
Take care of it by your side
Will it hurt a lot?
Yeah, search
Shamans have that kind of thing.
Even if you don’t take the medicine and go to the hospital, it’s no use.
You just have to suffer as a living child.
That too by the way
I'm sure he's not joking right now.
It's going to be very rotten and crumbly.
Why the heart?
What's going on?
It's housework
Uh, you don't have to know.
Ah, yes
Huh?
Anyway, looking at your handsome face
I hope it gets better
I don't know, me too
Don't worry too much
I'll do my best
How?
With a proud face?
It's really fun
Are you here?
Yeah
How was your grandmother?
Yeah, it went pretty well.
But they say it's a human talisman
Always stuck together
Because I'm away...
Strange, right?
Yeah
Make a room...
I think it's pretty
I've been thinking about it for a long time
It's cute...
Did you choose like this?
Yeah...
You must have been busy, but you studied a lot
Work hard...
It's not a thing...
Let’s save Bae Gyeon-woo, let’s save him?
What is this?
uh?
Give it to me
No, why, why, why?
What is this?
It's nothing
Oh, well, what is it?
Oh, don't read it.
fire ghost
don't read
Suicide ears?
Suicide ears are nothing?
Oh, I told you not to read it!
읽지 말라면 읽지 말지, 왜 자꾸 읽어
No...
- That's ah, ah...
- Give it to me.
Seongya
sorry, sorry
Are you still angry?
Sorry, I just...
I did something with that.
no
i am sorry
근데 나는 네가 몰랐으면 좋겠어
사람은 사람 안에서 살아야 돼
귀신이랑 연관되면
그 경계에서 살게 돼
I
you quickly
I wish it had nothing to do with us
평범해지면 좋겠어
Ah...
That's right
귀신 보게 된 거 알면
얼마나 속상해할까?
절대 안 들켜야겠다
Okay
don't worry too much
Isn't it
Seongya
Seongya, are you sleeping?
Uh, huh?
It's like this again
continue
It keeps doing this
이렇게 팔도 올려 봐요
Hey, you minors!
uh?
You...
You said I grew up holding hands, right?
ah!
hey! Hey, you old shaman.
He's hitting me often!
I'm not like that!
- hey!
- huh?
Uh...
Well, it's not like that.
Well, let me explain.
Ah, the soles of my feet.
Ah...
Hey, why are you so late...
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
you live
Have you ever felt very unfair?
i am like that now
my dream, my hope
Did everyone receive it well?
What I want to achieve
What I want to become, my future aspirations
You can write something like that roughly, right?
What else did you say to write roughly?
Conquer the Earth, Conquer the Universe
Don't even think about writing something like this.
And it doesn't matter if I don't have a dream, okay?
If you're not sure, just copy the people around you.
Okay then let's start
Anyway, it's still a dream
my dream?
Doctor, do you have a dream?
Will there be, no?
You don't have one either
Is there one?
butcher shop owner
Are you copying my dreams?
Do you want to do business together?
- I'll be the boss.
- Okay.
- call
- Huh?
Just
The insignificant thing is like you, huh
Park Seong-ah, come out
I thought you would
Bae Gyeon-woo?
you too
Now, read them both.
my dream is to be a college student
There is no department I want to go to
I definitely want to go to a 4-year program.
high school graduation ceremony
I want to go to the university entrance ceremony
I want to take a commemorative photo holding a bouquet of flowers.
Is it?
What I want to do now
Graduation and admission?
Uh...
Graduation ceremony and entrance ceremony
Oh, do I have to choose between the two?
Uh... then it's my graduation ceremony.
I've been to the entrance ceremony a few times.
I have never been to a graduation ceremony.
No?
Neither can work
It doesn't happen on its own over time.
It's something you can achieve if you work hard
Write it again, okay?
Is that something you can work on?
Next Gyeonwoo
By trying?
Uh...
My dream is...
I'll just write it next time
Okay, then, let's do that.
Get in quick, man
Why has this place been so empty since a while ago?
Did you go to the bathroom?
I'm a nerd, I haven't come to school yet
Ah, now even the nerd
Are you upset?
Yeah, this is my class.
This is our class, right?
Hey, why don't you announce it?
What did you write?
Ah, go...
Adult?
What, your dream is to become an adult?
Oh, give it to me, I'll change it
This doesn't mean you can work hard.
I want to change
Sseu-eup, how old is Bongsu?
Why is that happening all of a sudden?
than us
I thought I might be young
Wow, that's a bit...
Yeah, not so good
Yo, nerd!
Why are you so late?
You missed me!
Beomsaeng, are you in a lot of pain?
Take a good rest
What? Did you call me?
Suicide ears?
Oh, where on earth has he gone?
I'd like to at least give it a pinch of salt.
- Gyeonwoo.
- Huh?
I have urgent work to do
Can you let go of my hand for a moment?
Uh...
No, no.
Huh? no?
Yeah
No...
I said I would protect you
You have to catch it to protect it
your face turned red
Ah...
How can you not blush when you hear this?
no, that's not it
I think you're sick
ten, now
Huh?
ruined
Is this the start of a war?
A wooden box about this size.
The lid is tied to a white cloth so that it cannot be opened.
I'm carrying a box
There's no way he could have seen anything wrong with his powers.
Wooden box?
A wooden box about this size.
wooden box
The lid is tied to a white cloth so that it cannot be opened.
I'm carrying a box
A white cloth tied...
tied with a white cloth
wooden box tied with white cloth
Coffin?
Only one of the two will live
That's too much
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me, why? huh?
Why didn't you tell me, why did you hide it?
why!
Why did you hide it!
why! Why did you hide it, why!
Why...
Why did you hide it?
Why did you hide it!
why!
Why, why didn't you tell me...
my baby, my baby
my baby
On my back...
I can't even get to my back, I'm in a coffin...
Why didn't you tell me you were locked in a coffin, Mom?
Why didn't you tell me?
why!
Why did you hide it?
Why didn't you tell me, why...
It's chlorine!
-Why didn't you tell me, why!
- Chloride
-Why!
- It's chlorine!
Why don't you say something...
- Chloride
-Why...
-Why didn't you teach me?
why?
my baby...
On my back...
Seongya
Let's just go home, okay?
uh?
Oh no
If you don't practice archery even for a day,
My posture is messed up, I need to practice.
No, you hurt like this
What kind of practice is this, let's go
Wait a minute, I'll go wash my face and come back.
Yeah
Uh, sleep...
Hey
What were you excited about because I wasn’t there yesterday?
No, how much fun did you have?
Is the kid in that much pain?
It doesn't hurt
- Since the war
- A fight?
Shaman, what did you do?
I don't know either
Don't worry, I'll take good care of you.
What do you take care of?
I'm next to you now
you are in the mirror
Hey Gyeonwoo
Seongya
Look at this guy, he's in really bad condition.
Hey
I'm not a cowherd
I can't do it.
Let's go home, Seongya.
If you commit a big sin, you will be punished greatly.
Is being sick a big punishment?
Is it a big punishment for someone you love to be sick?
My loved one is hurting
It's a much bigger punishment
So
the sky instead of you
You're blaming your child.
You're sick
It hurts as harshly as the sin I committed.
I'll curse you until I die
No, I will curse you even when I die
I prayed the whole time
please forgive me
I'll curse you
Now you come?
no need
Cursing you?
I need my stuff
Aren't you going to curse?
Not a single day in 10 years
Since I didn't put it down, it will work well.
Cheer up and do it
Stop...
Please stop...
Stop!
Did you break all the chocolate?
- I'll do it.
- Huh?
- Get some rest.
- No...
But
Would that fit here?
Don't put it there
That box is not enough to contain my artistic soul.
too small
Bok...
I really don’t do what I’m told.
I didn't really listen to what people said.
Because you look like me!
Jinwoong Kim, are you crying now?
Hey, hey, Jinwoong, why are you crying?
Jinwoong-ah
Jinwoong?
Do-yeon told you to stop crying, right?
Doyeon was born before Bok?
It can't be reincarnation?
What does it matter!
I care about Doyeon
Loving is important
I think you're really crazy
Oh!
I'm crazy
I'm crazy about Doyeon
Stop crying, okay?
It's okay, it's okay
There's nothing more to break here, okay?
I'll destroy it all
That crazy kid over there, break it to pieces.
Okay
I'm just like, huh?
Will you destroy everything?
Wow, you think it’s a vibrating blender?
Can you turn off your phone?
Where are you going?
You're not replying?
After school, you know?
Come right after you finish
Starting today, come with your friend
A kid named Joo Seung
Huh?
Where did this go?
No way
Beomsaeng is not in a good mood right now.
What's going on?
Then just go to the teacher's office
Let's tell the teacher, okay?
I can't explain it, I have to do it
You shouldn't get involved with ghosts.
Seong-ah, Seong-ah, I don’t think this is the place
Just tell the teacher
Let's go, let's go
Let’s go, Seongya.
I'm sorry
Hey nerd, come out for a second.
I know what you're thinking
Open the door, okay?
uh?
Hey nerd, open the door
Seongya, let’s go first.
Wait a minute
Hey
You say you take care of a shaman?
If I let a suicidal demon go alone, will it be used?
Suicide ears?
nerd
don't think like that
That's not really what you think, just now
It's because it's so hard
Gyeonwoo, don’t think like that.
Grandma must be sad.
If I see you doing this
I'm the problem
Because of me, Joo Seung...
All you need is me
I'm sorry
Because I'm a bad luck grandmother
- I can't do it, Seong-ya.
- Huh?
Hold on tight, okay?
uh?
Bum, Bum Saeng!
Put it down
Guys
- I'm sorry.
- Huh? no!
Let go of this!
ah!
In the following order: Lee, Thursday, Nine, Nasal
being consumed by ghosts
Yeongseol, share your mouth
Why are you like this?
I can't hear my voice
Youngbi, you can even smell the scent of a ghost.
Is it the smell of incense?
Even if we get involved
Even if I die, I can't see blood
When skin irritation occurs
I can't control the situation
Being unable to live or die
That's the problem
Huh?
Uh...
Gyeonwoo, are you okay?
huh. It's better than I thought
Thank goodness
No, but I don’t think you’re okay?
uh?
Ah...
Oh, I see.
Umm
I think I'm feeling better now
A little? Uh...
To what extent can you walk now?
Yeah
Why does it hurt so much? Ah...
But do you really need to go to the hospital for this?
Yeah, it's really okay.
But
How many days have you not practiced archery?
Archery?
Has it been 2 or 3 days?
uh?
Oh no, let's go practice archery.
Oh no, no, no
What, what do you mean, it hurts like this, I can’t
No, I'm really better now.
Oh no
Ah
Look at this, am I really okay?
It's cute, but oh, no, no, no.
No, Seongya.
Huh?
Ah...
Oh, be surprised.
When are you going to tell me the truth?
uh?
Suddenly what?
cowherd
Why me?
Bongsuya
What is Bongsu, all of a sudden?
Because you are Bongsu
no, suddenly
What are you talking about, Seongya?
When you shoot a bow
I don't do this, routine.
No, that's...
You're not Gyeonwoo, you're Bongsu.
Seong-ah, why are you so scary?
Bongsuya
What about Gyeonherd?
Where is Gyeonwoo?
I...
I ate it
Chlorination
The intention is to call the grim reaper.
I want to live as a person
His body is completely
Please tell me how I can have it
When you become a person
Who even loves me?
- Are you two dating?
- Ah, I like it one-sidedly.
It's unrequited love
Are you... going to be nice to me?
Yes
I am Baekyeonwoo.
The person in front of you is Bae Gyeon-woo
Gyeonwoo, I will put it back properly.
Until then, please stay safe
Aren’t you curious about the truth of the fairy of heaven and earth?
Check it out yourself